export const QuizData = [
    {
        question:"Which of the following is used in React.js to increase performance",
        options:["Original DOM","Virtual DOM","Both A and B","None of the above"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question:"what is ReactJS",
        options:["Server-side framework","no framework","user interface framework","None of the above"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question:"Identify the one which is used to pass data to components from outside",
        options:["Render with Arguments","setState","propTypes","props"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question:"Who created React.js",
        options:["Jordan Walke","Jordan Mike","Tim Lee","Jordan Lee"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"In Which language is React.js written",
        options:["Java","Python","JavaScipt","PHP"],
        answer:3
    }
    ,
    {
        question:"What is Babel",
        options:["JavaScript Compiler","JavaScript Interpreter","JavaScript transpiler","None of the above"],
        answer:1
    }
    ,
    {
        question:"How many elements can a valid react component return",
        options:["2","1","3","4"],
        answer:2
    }
    ,
    {
        question:"A state in React.js is also known as",
        options:["External Storage of the component","Permanent Storage","The Internal Storage of the component","All of the above"],
        answer:3
    }
    ,
    {
        question:"What are arbitrary inputs of components in react also known as",
        options:["Elements","keys","Ref","Props"],
        answer:4
    },
    {
        question:"Among The following options, choose the one which helps react for keeping their data uni-directional",
        options:["DOM","Flux","JSX","Props"],
        answer:2
    }
];